88 chunks total. Showing all 1 from housing_morrow_house_noise.txt.

Paste these into your README under Sample Chunks. The rubric asks
for the source file and the function that produced them ù both are
printed for you below.

======================================================================
Chunk 1  |  source: housing_morrow_house_noise.txt#0  |  produced by: chunker.py::split_documents
======================================================================
Housing

Noise levels in Morrow House

Asked about this a lot so writing it down. Loud until about 1am on weekends, no enforced quiet hours.

If you're someone who needs quiet to work, the library is open until 2am during term and that's what most people in this building end up doing.

For each one, ask: could someone answer a question using only this,
without reading what came before or after?
